<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MotorBro</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">238165707334677</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb238165707334677</string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy1">
        MotorBro Privacy Policy
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolic1Desc">
        Welcome to DateFilipina Privacy Policy (\"Policy\")! This explains how we collect, store, protect, and share your information, and with whom we share it. We suggest you read this in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use. Whilst you\'re using the DateFilipina mobile application ("App"), we collect some information about you. In addition, you may choose to use the App to share information with other DateFilipina users, including your friends and contacts ("Users"). We may also need to share your information sometimes.
<br />
DateFilipina is a global app, and your information will be sent to and used in the Philippines regardless of the country you reside in. This Policy explains how we protect your personal data when we transfer it overseas, so please read very carefully!
<br />
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please feel free to contact us at feedback@team.datefilipina.com.
<br />
    </string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy2">
        1. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolic2Desc">
       Registration Information
        <br />
When you download the App and create an account ("Account"), we may collect certain information ("Registration Information") about you, such as:
<br />
Name;
Username;
Email address;
Mobile number;
Gender identity;
Date of birth;
Sexual preference;
Photographs;
Location; and
        <br />
Login information and friend lists for social media accounts that you connect to your Bumble Account (this could include, for example, your Facebook and Instagram accounts ("Social Media Accounts").
<br />
        You will also be required to create a password in connection with the registration of your Account. Once you register, you will be able to review and change this information at any time by accessing your “Profile” page! You control your user profile and are able to correct or update (other than your email address, mobile number, date of birth, gender and location (which is automatically updated)) your information at any time by just logging in to Bumble.
<br />
The information we collect helps to enhance the App and verify our Users. Registration Information such as your name and username may be visible to the public on your profile page.
<br />
Additional Information
        <br />
We may ask you to provide your full name, address and email address. Such details may be shared with third parties for purposes relating to, for example, any of our loyalty programs, sending gifts or delivery of merchandise.
<br />
We may also collect additional information in connection with your use of DateFilipina.
<br />
If you contact our Customer Support team, we will receive your email address, and may track your IP address as well as the information you send to us to help resolve your query. We will keep records of our communications with you, including any complaints that we receive from you about other Users (and from other Users about you).
<br />
We recommend and encourage you (and all our members) to think carefully about the information you disclose about yourself. We also do not recommend that you put email addresses, URLs, instant messaging details, phone numbers, full names or addresses, credit card details, national identity numbers, drivers licence details and other sensitive information on your profile which is open to abuse and misuse.
<br />
Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself on your profile such as your religious denomination and health details. While you may voluntarily provide this information to us when you create your profile, including your sexual preferences, there is no requirement to do so. Please remember that photographs that you post on DateFilipina may reveal information about yourself as well. Where you do upload and choose to tell us sensitive information about yourself, you are explicitly consenting to our processing of your information and making this public to other users.
<br />
When you post information about yourself or use the messaging function, the amount of personal information you share is at your own risk. Please see Section 4 below for more information on who can access what you post on DateFilipina. If you post anything that is inconsistent with our Terms and Conditions of Use, we reserve the right to terminate your Account.
<br />
For safety and security and to ensure you have the best possible user experience, we require users to verify their accounts and might ask for your phone number. And we also want to avoid fake DateFilipina accounts being created which can be used for malicious activities and cybercrime – they threaten the DateFilipina network and spoil things for everyone. We use a third party provider for account verification who will keep your phone number for up to 90 days for fraud identification purposes across a range of online platforms and services like DateFilipina’s.
<br />
To prevent abuse of the app/site, DateFilipina uses automated decisions to block accounts as part of its anti-spam procedures. In order to do this, our systems check accounts and messages for content that indicates breaches of our Terms and Conditions of Use. If an account or message meets certain criteria that demonstrate that the Terms and Conditions of Use are likely to have been breached, the relevant account will automatically be blocked. All users of accounts that have been blocked will be notified that their account has been blocked and affected users can contact Bumble to contest the decision.
<br />
If you decide to purchase any of our premium services, we will process your payment information and retain this securely for the prevention of fraud and for audit/tax purposes.
<br />
Finally, we want to keep in touch with you to make sure you know about the great promotions and offers we have available. If you’ve told us it’s OK, we will use your email address and phone number to send you information on these. You can withdraw this consent at any time via Settings in the app.
<br /><br />
Data Storage
        <br />
By using the App, you acknowledge that DateFilipina is a global app operating through servers located in a number of countries around the world, including the Philippines. If you live in a country with data protection laws, the storage of your personal data may not provide you with the same protections as you enjoy in your country of residence.
<br /><br />
Geolocation Information
        <br />
If you turn these features on, when you use your mobile, we will collect information about WiFi access points as well as other location information about your longitude and latitude and may save your device\'s coordinates to offer certain features to you. This information helps us identify your physical location and we may use it to personalise the App and make it easier for you to interact with other Users, by enabling the information to be displayed and shared with other members choosing to view “nearby” posts.
<br />If you have enabled location services, but wish to turn them off, you can do so by the following methods:
<br />Android — settings, location, DateFilipina, permissions, location.
<br /><br />

<br />Log and Usage Data<br />
<br />We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes (as set out in Section 11 below) and as permitted by applicable law.
<br />In practice, we delete or anonymise your information upon deletion of your account (following the safety retention window), unless:
<br />1.	We must keep it to comply with applicable law (for instance, some “traffic data” is kept for one year to comply with statutory data retention obligations);
<br />2.	We must keep it to evidence our compliance with applicable law (for instance, records of consents to our Terms, Privacy Policy and other similar consents are kept for five years);
<br />3.	There is an outstanding issue, claim or dispute requiring us to keep the relevant information until it is resolved; or
<br />4.	The information must be kept for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud prevention and enhancing users\' safety and security. For example, information may need to be kept to prevent a user who was banned for unsafe behaviour or security incidents from opening a new account.

<br /><br />
Device Information
<br />We may collect information about your device when you use the App including the unique device identifier, device model, operating system, and MAC address. In addition, if you permit us to do so, the App may access your device\'s address book solely in order to add someone to your contacts.
<br /><br />
Links
<br />We may keep track of how you interact with links available on DateFilipina including third party services and clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We may share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.
<br /><br />
Cookies<br />
<br />Cookies are small data files that are transferred to your computer\'s hard disk and are basically a tool that stores information about website visits, recognises you and your preferences each time you visit DateFilipina, and ensures site functionality and enables us to provide the services our member’s request.
<br /><br />
The cookies we collect enable us to learn how people interact with DateFilipina, which in turn helps us make a better product for you! Cookies store information about your website visits and can recognise you and your preferences each time you visit the DateFilipina site. They help us to provide a better service to you!
<br />
DateFilipina’s use of cookies and local storage devices is basically related to the performance of DateFilipina\’s site, such as analytics that help us determine how our site is performing and ensuring a smooth and trouble-free experience for our members and visitors.
<br />
Below is a table to explain DateFilipina’s cookie functions and why they’re used.
<br />
If for any reason you decide that you do not want all of your DateFilipina activities to be stored you may set your browser and mobile settings to block cookies and local storage devices, but please remember that if you do so, you may not be able to access all of the features DateFilipina offers!
<br />
We use the following types of cookies:
<br />Cookie Functions	Cookie Purposes
<br />Analytics and research	We use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the App, where visitors have come from and the pages they visited. For more information about Google\'s Privacy Policy, please visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/.
<br />Performance	We need to use certain cookies and save data to your local storage devices to ensure our members have the best possible experience. They assist with your navigation of our site, ensuring pages load quickly and respond promptly to your requests.
<br />Our use of cookies and local storage devices, including the specific cookie names, may change over time, but will generally fall into the above categories. We will notify you of any important changes to our use of cookies and local storage devices. Please visit this page regularly so that you are aware of any changes.
<br /><br />
<br />If you would like to know more about cookies, including flash cookies/local storage devices, the following websites provide useful information:
<br />
<br />•	www.allaboutcookies.org
<br />•	www.youronlinechoices.eu
<br />•	http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html

    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy3">
2. USE OF INFORMATION.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy3Desc">
<br />
<br />In order to deliver an enjoyable experience to you, we may use your Registration and other information to:
<br />
<br />•	offer you our services and features;
<br />•	contact you with information about the App (e.g., updates and new offerings);
<br />•	personalise the App and the content we deliver to you;
<br />•	conduct research and analytics about how you use and interact with the App;
<br />•	resolve disputes between you and other Users; and
<br />•	investigate fraud, protect our legal rights, and to enforce our Terms and Conditions.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy4">
3. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy4Desc">
<br />Our policy is to not disclose your Registration Information, except in the limited circumstances described here:

<br />Your Consent – If you consent, we may share or disclose your Registration Information, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your Account.

<br />Service Providers - We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your Registration Information with these third parties, but only for the purposes of performing these functions and providing such services e.g. information technology companies (hardware and software) which provide services to support our products.

<br />Moderators – To monitor activity on the apps and approve content.

<br />Payment Processing and Telecommunications Companies – To facilitate payments for our premium services.

<br />Law and Harm - As we mentioned in the Terms and Conditions, we think it is very important that all Users behave whilst using the App. We will cooperate with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. We will also cooperate with law enforcement enquiries from within or outside your country of residence where we are required to by law or to protect the vital interests of a person. This may include preserving or disclosing any of your information, including your Registration Information, if we believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with a law or regulation, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues e.g. through anti-spam providers to protect the service from criminal activity or to protect our rights or property or those of third parties. In such cases we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

<br />Business Transfers -In the event that DateFilipina or any of our affiliates undergoes a business transition or change of ownership, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, re-organisation, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, or in the event of insolvency or administration, we may be required to disclose your personal data.

<br />Aggregated Information – We may share aggregated information with third parties that includes your personal data (but which doesn’t identify you directly) together with other information including log data for industry analysis and demographic profiling. You may opt-out of receiving marketing messages by using the opt-out mechanisms and links provided in each email.
<br />We ensure these parties must adhere to strict data protection and confidentiality provisions that are consistent with this Policy. Measures are taken to ensure that the data shared is non-attributable to the greatest extent possible.

<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy5">
<b>4.	WHAT OTHERS MAY SEE ABOUT YOU.</b>
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy5Desc">
<br />Our App is designed to make it easier for you to connect with other Users and to interact with them. If you register or login to the App using your Facebook account, you are authorising us to access certain Facebook account information, including information you make available via Facebook, your friends list, current location and those friends you have in common with other Users. You also understand that your DateFilipina profile and other information you make available via the App, including information you provide directly or indirectly through Facebook (i.e., your Facebook photos, your name, age, approximate location, friends you have in common with other Users and other profile information), may be viewed and shared by Users with individuals who may or may not be Users or via third party applications in such Users’ discretion. For example, a User may recommend you as a match to his or her Facebook friends by sharing your picture, regardless of whether such friend(s) is also a User of the App. You might share information like the photos and messages you send or upload and any metadata provided with those messages, along with any comments or information you provide in connection with your photos.
<br />
<br />When using DateFilipina, you should assume that anything you post or submit on the App may be publicly-viewable and accessible, both by Users of the App and non-Users of the App. We want our Users to be careful about posting information that will eventually be made public.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy6">
<b>5. MODIFYING YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION.</b>
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy6Desc">
<br />You may access or modify the Registration Information you provided at anytime or permanently delete your Account.
<br />When your Account is deactivated, we take reasonable efforts to make sure it is no longer viewable on the App. For up to 30 days it is still possible to restore your Account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated. After 30 days, we begin the process of deleting your Account from our systems. We are not responsible for any information, pictures, comments, or other content that is deleted from our systems resulting from the deactivation of your Account.
<br />
<br />To prevent abuse and/or misuse of DateFilipina by a User following termination or deletion of a profile/Account we shall retain such information as we deem in our sole discretion may be necessary to ensure that User does not open a new Account and profile in breach of our Terms and Conditions of Use and to ensure compliance with all laws and regulations.
<br />Warning: Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your Account, copies of that information may still be viewable and/or accessed to the extent such information has been previously shared with others, or copied or stored by other Users or to the extent such information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control this, nor do we accept any liability for this. If you have given third party applications or websites access to your personal information they may retain such information to the extent permitted under their terms of service or privacy policies.
<br />Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 30 days to enable restoration, but will not be available to others in the meantime.
<br /><br />  </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy7">
        <b>6. OUR POLICY TOWARDS AGE.</b>
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy7Desc">
<br />Although we want as many people as possible to enjoy our creation, you have to be at least 18 years old to use the App.
<br />DateFilipina does not knowingly collect any information about or market to children, minors or anyone under the age of 18. If you are less than 18 years old, we request that you do not submit information to us. If we become aware that a child, minor or anyone under the age of 18 has registered with us and provided us with personal information, we will take steps to terminate that person\'s registration and delete their Registration Information from DateFilipina. If we do delete a profile because you violated our no children rules, we may retain your email and IP address to ensure that you do not try to get around our rules by creating a new profile.
<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy8">
        <b>7. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY.</b>
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy8Desc">
<br />As DateFilipina evolves, we may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at bumble.com/privacy/. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you, for example, via an email to the email associated with your Account or by posting a notice within DateFilipina. By continuing to access or use the App after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy9">
        8. SECURITY.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy9Desc">
<br />Here at DateFilipina we pride ourselves on taking commercially reasonable security measures to help protect your information against loss, misuse and unauthorised access, or disclosure. We use reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information such as secured servers using firewalls.
<br />Unfortunately no website or Internet transmission is ever completely 100% secure and even we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access, hacking, data loss or other breaches will never occur, but here are some handy tips to help keep your data secure:
<br />1.	Please make sure you log out of your Account after use as you never know who may stumble onto your Account!
<br />2.	Please don\'t share your social media password with anyone else!
<br />3.	Change your social media password periodically.
<br />If you ever think someone has had access to your social media password, please report it to the relevant social media platform and change your password immediately. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal data while it is being transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk.

<br /><br />
<br />WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO ANY BREACHES OF SECURITY, DAMAGE TO YOUR DEVICE, OR ANY LOSS OR UNAUTHORISED USE OF YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION OR OTHER DATA.
<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy10">
        9. THIRD PARTY ACCOUNTS.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy10Desc">
<br />If you have registered with DateFilipina using a third party social media platform, such as Facebook, your DateFilipina profile will be available to all Users of DateFilipina whether via our App or our partners\' websites.
<br />Remember that when you register with a third party, you are also giving them personal information, so we recommend that you read their privacy policies as DateFilipina does not control how they use their information.
<br />If you have registered on one of these third party websites, such as Facebook, or you have verified your Account via a third party website, we may connect your DateFilipina profile with your profile on such website. We may do this by way of new products and applications which we introduce from time to time, including new products powered by our group companies.
<br />If you have created a DateFilipina profile through a third party website and you do not want to link your DateFilipina profile to your profile on the third party website, DateFilipina cannot amend these settings. Please visit the application settings on your third party website profile and follow the instructions to remove the DateFilipina access permissions.
<br />We only use the APIs, OAuth Tokens, Widgets, or other means provided by the applicable Social Media Account to integrate your Social Media Account with our App. As such, we only receive the limited information that each Social Media Account permits to be transferred.
<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy11">
        10. ABOUT US.
    </string>

    <string name="privacyPolicy11Desc">
<br />Your access to the App, as well as this Privacy Policy are governed and interpreted by the laws of the State of New York, other than such laws, rules, regulations and case law that would result in the application of the laws of a jurisdiction other than the State of New York. By using the App, you are consenting to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the United States and the State of New York. You agree that such courts shall have in personam jurisdiction and venue and waive any objection based on inconvenient forum. You agree that you will not file or participate in a class action against us. In the event there is a discrepancy between this English language version and any translated copies of the Policy, the English version shall prevail.
<br />Effective date
<br />This Privacy Policy was last updated on 16 December 2019.
<br /><br />
    </string>

    <string name="termsServicesDescription">
        DateFilipina provides a service for single adults to meet each other online, it\'s operated by Elevin Tech. By using the DateFilipina application, (the "App") you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use (this "Agreement"), whether or not you register as a member of DateFilipina ("Member"). If you wish to become a Member and make use of the DateFilipina service (the "Service"), please read these Terms and Conditions. If you object to anything in this Agreement, do not use the App or the Service.
    </string>

    <string name="termsServices1">
        1. DateFilipina RULES
    </string>

    <string name="termsServices1Desc">
        Before you can use our App, you will need to register for an account ("Account"). In order to create an Account you must:
	1.
be at least 18 years old; and
	2.
be legally permitted to use the App by the laws of your home country.


You can create an Account via manual registration, or by using your Facebook login details. If you create an Account using your Facebook login details, you authorise us to access, display and use certain information from your Facebook account (e.g. profile pictures, relationship status, location and information about Facebook friends). For more information about what information we use and how we use it, please check out our Privacy Policy.
It is not allowed to use another person\'s Account without permission.
You can delete your Account at any time by going to the \Settings\' page when you are logged in and clicking on the \'Delete account\' link. Your Account will be deleted immediately but it may take a little while for Your Content (defined below) to be completely removed from the App. We will save your profile information and if you decide to restore your Account (which you can do within 30 days of de-activating your Account). If you delete your Account and try to create a new account within this time period using the same credentials, we will re-activate your Account for you. We reserve the right at our sole discretion to terminate or suspend any Account, or make use of any operational, technological, legal or other means available to enforce the Terms (including without limitation blocking specific IP addresses), at any time without liability and without the need to give you prior notice.
You may not access, tamper with, or use non-public areas of the App or our systems. Certain portions of the App may not be accessible if you have not registered for an Account.
    </string>

    <string name="termsServices2">
        User information
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices2Desc">
        You represent, warrant, and undertake that the information and photos that you supply to the App is/are accurate in all respects.
Apart from the above, you must not upload on our website images that contain:
	*
graphic in nature;
	*
depiction of underage;
	*
low quality;
	*
inappropriate(nude, sexual, violence).
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices3">
        Own risk
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices3Desc">
        You accept that your use of the App and it\'s Service is solely at your own risk.
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices4">
        Certain Contents that are not allowed on DateFilipina
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices4Desc">
        contains language or imagery which could be deemed offensive or is likely to harass, upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person;
	*
is obscene, pornographic, violent or otherwise may offend human dignity;
	*
is abusive, insulting or threatening, discriminatory or which promotes or encourages racism, sexism, hatred or bigotry;
	*
encourages any illegal activity including, without limitation, terrorism, inciting racial hatred or the submission of which in itself constitutes committing a criminal offence;
	*
is defamatory or libellous;
	*
relates to commercial activities (including, without limitation, sales, competitions and advertising, links to other websites or premium line telephone numbers);
	*
involves the transmission of "junk" mail or "spam";
	*
contains any spy ware, adware, viruses, corrupt files, worm programmes or other malicious code designed to interrupt, damage or limit the functionality of or disrupt any software, hardware, telecommunications, networks, servers or other equipment, Trojan horse or any other material designed to damage, interfere with, wrongly intercept or expropriate any data or personal information whether from DateFilipina or otherwise;
	*
itself, or the posting of which, infringes any third party\'s rights (including, without limitation, intellectual property rights and privacy rights);
	*
shows another person which was created or distributed without that person’s consent.


DateFilipina operates a zero-tolerance policy for this kind of content.
    </string>

    <string name="termsServices5">
        Content Of Profile
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices5Desc">
        1.
You are solely responsible for the content of your profile, messages, video and audio recordings and other materials you may upload to the Service or transmit to other members of the Service.
	2.
You agree that you will not upload to your profile or onto the Website any content which is abusive, obscene, profane, offensive, sexually oriented, threatening, harassing, racially offensive, improper or otherwise inappropriate as determined at our sole discretion or has graphics, a photo of underage, celebrities.

    </string>
    <string name="termsServices6">
        Interaction with members
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices6Desc">
        You are solely responsible for your interaction with other members of the Service and the App.

    </string>
    <string name="termsServices7">
        Information not confidential
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices7Desc">
        You agree that any material or information provided by you, save and except for any Personal Information (which may include your full name, postal address, telephone number etc.), the use of which is governed by our Privacy Policy, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and we may use such material or information without restriction. You acknowledge that any such material or information provided by you will be available for other members or users of the Website to read.Risks
You acknowledge that there are risks involved in online dating, including but not limited to:
	1.
unknowingly dealing with underage persons
	2.
persons acting under a false profile or information
	3.
for a criminal purpose or fraudulent acts including without limitation, scamming or spamming.


You agree to take all necessary precautions when communicating with or meeting with other users, especially if you decide to meet in person. In addition, you agree to review our online dating safety reminders prior to using the service.Identity of the member
You acknowledge that the App cannot and does not warranty that each member or user of the Service or the App is who he or she claims to be, in view of the fact that user authentication is extremely difficult on the internet. The App does not warrant that member profiles are reliable, accurate or complete. Consequently, you must be careful in dealing with other members or users of the App.
Account Terminated by us
We may immediately terminate your account and your access to the Service at any time if we determine (in our absolute discretion) that you have breached this Agreement. Notice of termination will be delivered to the last email address you provide to us.

    </string>

    <string name="termsServices8">
        Monitor Information
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices8Desc">
        The App reserve the right to monitor all profiles, messages, chat, and instant messages to ensure that they conform to the requirements of these Terms of Use.

    </string>

    <string name="termsServices9">
        Information Security
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices9Desc">
        Transmission of data over the internet cannot be guaranteed as being totally secured. We do not warrant and cannot ensure the security of any information you provide to us while we make great efforts protecting your information. Accordingly, any information which you provide to us is solely at your own risk. Nevertheless, once we receive your information, we will take reasonable steps to preserve the security of such information.
    </string>

    <string name="termsServices10">
        Information Security
    </string>
    <string name="termsServices10Desc">
        Transmission of data over the internet cannot be guaranteed as being totally secured. We do not warrant and cannot ensure the security of any information you provide to us while we make great efforts protecting your information. Accordingly, any information which you provide to us is solely at your own risk. Nevertheless, once we receive your information, we will take reasonable steps to preserve the security of such information.
Indemnification and Warranty
Under no circumstances, including but not limited to, negligence, shall Elevin Tech  or any of its related, affiliated companies be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use the Service. Subscriber specifically acknowledges and agrees that Elevin Tech  is not liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any user, or for any failure of error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of or use of records, whether under contract or tort theory, or under any other cause of action, for any amount over and above the amount paid by Subscriber to a Elevin Tech site.
Elevin Tech makes no warranties or representations as to the information, services or products provided through or in connection with the service. Subscriber\'s use of the service is at his/her own risk. Elevin Tech , nor any party involved in creating, producing, or delivering the server or content is liable for any direct incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive damages arising from your access to, use of, or interpretation of, the service or products or services or information provided by or through the service. Without limiting the foregoing, Elevin Tech  makes no warranty of merchantability, fitness for any purpose, or non- results of the use of the content in terms of their correctness, accuracy, timeliness, reliability or otherwise.
Member agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Elevin Tech, their officers, directors, managers, members, agents and employees from any against any claims, losses, liabilities or expenses (including reasonable attorneys\' fees) arising out of Subscriber\'s breach of any term, condition or promise contained herein. Should any such claim for indemnification arise, or should any action be brought by Subscriber or Elevin Tech  relating to any services or products offered by or through the Service, Subscriber agrees to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of The Philippines. Should any such claim for indemnification arise, or should any action be brought by subscriber or Elevin Tech  relating to any services or products offered by or through the Service Member agrees to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of The Philippines.
This Agreement sets forth the full and complete understanding between Subscriber and Elevin Tech  with respect to its subject matter, and supersedes all prior understanding or agreements, whether written or verbal. This Agreement may be modified upon notice by Elevin Tech  to its Subscribers. Unless contrary to law or otherwise stated, each provision of this Agreement shall survive termination. This Agreement shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of The Philippines for contracts entered into and wholly performed within that Country. The prevailing party in any suit to enforce the terms hereof shall be entitled to recover his/her/its reasonable attorneys\' fees.

    </string>
</resources>
